这节课的开始，我们会在forecastfragment.java文件中
We'll start by adding our call back functions
添加回调函数
to our forecast fragment. Now know we have two
我们有两个不同的loaderCallBacks回调函数选项，我们要
different options here for loader call backs. We want to
确保选中的是 "android.support.v4" 包里的这个回调函数
make sure that we're choosing the android.support.v4 callback so
这样我们就能使得应用在 Gingerbread（2.3版本） 系统上兼容。这是一个泛型类
we're compatible with Gingerbread. These take a generic
我们将会使用 cursor，是的，
type. We're going to want to use cursor. And yes that
就是 Android.database.cursor，现在让我们向下翻到
is Andriod.database.cursor. Now, let's move down to where we
我们要插入代码的地方，就在最下面这里
want to actually insert this code. Here at the bottom
当然，实际上可以用“Ctrl+I”快捷键来插入代码
and, of course, we use control I to actually insert.
我们的Cursor加载器模式被完美地插入在了这里
And there we have it beautifully, our loader pattern with cursor.
现在我们来做一些对我们有用的工作。首先，
Now let's do some work that will help us out. First
我们在这个ForecastFragment的最上面添加一个记录列的数组
we add an array of columns to the top of our forecast fragment.
这些列是会在我们的数据库查询中所使用的
These are the columns that are going to be used in our
注意，因为WeatherEntry 和 LocationEntry都有_ID
query. Note, that since both weather entry and location entry have
所以我们必须完整地描述哪一个ID
the underscore ID field, we must fully qualify, which ID we
才是我们在想在查询结果中列出来的
want in our projection for this query to work. And in
事实上，这个查询方法需要一个projection才能使用
fact, this query requires a projection to work at
否则的话就是模拟两可的 接下来，这里是一些和
all, otherwise that's ambiguous. Next, here are indexes that
FORECAST_COLUMNS捆绑在一起的指数。这将会使我们后面的工作
are tied to these columns. This'll make some of
变得更加简单。注意，看这些，实际上它们必须是相互对应的
our work easier, later on. Note, that these actually must
接下来我们创建一些 public 的指数
match. Then we create some public indexes to use,
供我们在adapter中使用，这会使得我们在adapter
in our adapter. This allows us to make our
中的代码简洁有效。但是这意味着
code tiny and efficient, in the adapter. But it
我们必须维持column index和projection之间的关系
means, we must maintain the relationship between these column indexes.
每一个loader都有一个ID
and the projection. Each loader has an ID. It
它允许在同一时间一个fargment中能有多个活跃的loader
allows a fragment to have multiple loaders active at
我们将把这个ID和一个变量一起放在这个类的最上面
once. We're going to place this along with an instance
这个变量用于储存我们的位置信息
variable to save off our location here at the
接下来我们将重载
top of our class. Next we're going to override
onActivityCreated函数。Loader在onActivityCreated函数
onActivityCreated. Loaders are initialized
中初始化，因为loader的生命周期是
in onActivityCreated because their life
和这个activity绑定到一起的，而不是和fragment
cycle is actually bound to the activity. Not the
请注意这个loader ID的使用 —— FORECAST_LOADER
fragment. Note the use of the loader ID. FORECAST_LOADER.
然后我们回到onCreateLoader这个函数
Then we return to the onCreateLoader function.
我们添加一个新的CursorLoader，这个CursorLoader有我们的查询方法
We add a new CursorLoader. This CursorLoader has
包括 start date，colums和sort order。
our query, including start date, columns, and sort
我们的start date实际上在我们的URI中
order. Our start date is actually in our
column就是我们之前定义的，并且sort order是
URI. Our columns are the ones we defined earlier, and our sort order is going
基于COLUMN_DATETEXT升序的
to be based upon COLUMN_DATETEXT ascending. Let's do
让我们做一遍最后的检查，我们要确保我们使用
one last check. We want to make sure we're
了这些类的支持库版本
using the support library version of all of
否则，我们无法兼容Android 2.3版本
these classes, otherwise we won't get Android 2.3 compatibility.